notes please invite your people invite
your people
invite your people listen
um so as you all know every fourth
Sabbath or last Sabbath of the month we
do evangelism Sabbath and
um we'll we'll take a particular
Doctrine and the target audience is you
know people who may have never heard you
know of these teachings before
and so uh this this week I knew was
evangelism it was evangelism Sabbath and
I knew what I was going to be talking
about I was going to be talking about
the Book of Daniel chapter 7.
um particularly about the little horn
in Daniel chapter 7.
and
um
so I wasn't really you know too worried
I listen y'all I can
I can give a Daniel 7 sermon probably
sleeping okay
so
I wasn't too worried about that
um
I
was waiting until Friday
to kind of just bring it all together
and some things started to happen
throughout the day yesterday that
pushed my allotted time to put my sermon
together down into the evening
down into the nighttime by
we were having some some things that we
had to work out
um some technological issues we had to
work out
and so what ends up happening is
you know I'm we're getting into 11 11 30
at night
and I have not yet
been able to even put a thought
to what I'm going to preach
and while we're uh getting these things
prepared for for the message today
uh actually throughout the day I had
been getting warnings put that in the
chat for me y'all I've been getting
warnings put that word in the chat
warning so I was getting text messages I
was
you know getting alerts on my phone and
you know it's like okay you know another
storm coming and whatever but maybe it's
gonna pass
and so around
11 30 11 no I'm sorry even later even
later I think it was later
I think it's like 12
15 and we're we're still up dealing with
some of these these issues to be ready
for today
and then the sirens go off
um
and the rain starts pouring down
and atanta is like we need to go because
this is bad usually the storms will pass
over the area in which we live in in
Alabama but uh in Huntsville but this
time it didn't
and so we ended up having to leave what
we were doing with our volunteers still
you know they're they're elsewhere and
they're
um you know they're plugged into my
computer so they can continue to do what
they're doing but I was like guys I got
we gotta run
and what happens is we leave and we go
to our next door uh uh neighbors who
have a shelter uh in their garage we've
got a shelter as well but but their
shelter is more sturdy
so we were there probably for about 35
to 40 minutes and the whole time I'm
just thinking I am so tired right now
I am so tired right now and I haven't
even begun
to put together
my message and some of y'all already
beat me to the chat are you already beat
me to the punch in the chat you're
already talking about sirens and and
warnings are you already see this
but what's funny is as we were there at
our neighbors
um
and uh there we have Muslim neighbors
and so we were talking and you know they
start Ramadan
yesterday I think and we were talking
talking and they you know I was letting
her know that you know we've you know
preaching to I'll be preaching tomorrow
and then both her and my wife were like
you should preach about tornadoes
and I'm like you know and I'm actually
said to my wife yeah uh I'm gonna be
preaching on Daniel 7. and she's like
you just need to time tornadoes and I
was like a tante and then
that was it we came back to the house
and at 1am in the morning
no at 1 30 in the morning
pulled out my computer
and now it's time to put the message
together and so now you understand why
the message for today is entitled I'm
gonna put this up on the screen
the coming
tornado
let's pray Heavenly Father
speak to us Lord
open our eyes
this is our prayer in Jesus name
amen
amen the coming tornado
so this this tornado really kind of took
us
a little bit by surprise not really we
were getting warnings throughout the day
but
as the the day kept going on and you
know it kind of looked really nice
outside and then the day changed like it
it just things just got different
and after we you know we realized man
these winds are really really like
coming hard these winds are really
coming hard what happened is you know we
ended up running for shelter we we went
to our next door neighbors and you know
let us in we went into the we didn't we
we they have us a very
sturdy Rock Solid
shelter
I remember after we came back and you
know I was thinking about this concept
of this of this storm and you know tati
was telling me I was watching the news
and they said that it started in the
Gulf of Mexico that's where the the
tornado you know that's where it started
the Gulf of Mexico
um
and
I really started thinking
something just hit my mind some just
came to me and I'm gonna go to the
screen and I just want you to see here
um this is from The Washington Post
and the article the headline of the
article says the Gulf of Mexico is very
warm that could mean a bad tornado
season a bad tornado season and inside
the article here's what it says
water temperatures in the Gulf of Mexico
often enter the conversation during
Hurricane Season but they also play a
role in tornado season each spring
concern is growing for the potential
impact that that abnormally warms sea
surface temperatures will have in the
weeks and months ahead with a with
experts warily keeping tabs on what
could be a busy tornado season
currently the waters are up to several
degrees warmer than normal and as a high
and as a high
and as high as the upper 70s and I just
wanted to take that little segment just
to point out this this
how the the temperature of the waters
how the the the these tornadoes have
their origin maybe not all of them but
many of them have their origin in this
gulf because
of the temperature
water is located there
and I began to think to myself how
interesting
how absolutely interesting because
the Bible speaks of an ultimate
tornado
that is coming
the Bible speaks of an ultimate tornado
and last night I actually or this
morning I should say I actually looked
up the definition of the word tornado
and here's what it said I'm gonna put it
on the screen a mobile
destructive vortex
of violently rotating winds having the
appearance of a funnel-shaped cloud and
advancing beneath a large storm system
and when I read that that description a
destructive Vortex of violently rotating
winds like I couldn't help but think
who in the world would want to be caught
up in a Vortex of violently rotating
wind
like I just had this imagery of you know
people in the middle of this of this
tornado and it's like there's no Escape
people in the middle of this tornado
there's no way out because the winds are
so strong and and it brought my mind it
brought me to Revelation chapter seven
it brought me to Revelation chapter 7
verse 1 where the Bible reads after
these things I saw four Angels standing
on the four corners of the Earth holding
the Four Winds of the earth that the
wind should not blow on the earth nor on
the sea nor on any tree and I saw
another Angel ascending from the East
having the Seal of the Living God and he
cried with a loud voice
to the four angels to whom it was given
to hurt the earth and the Sea saying
hurt not the Earth neither the sea nor
the trees till we have sealed the
Servants of our God in their foreheads
now I want y'all to understand
that Revelation chapter 7
is in fact
describing a coming whirlwind
it is describing a coming storm and the
only way God's people are protected from
this storm
ultimately is them receiving the Seal of
God in their foreheads and so what I
want you to do right now is simply focus
on this idea
that the Bible describes a storm that's
coming at the end of time a tornado
that is going to touch down on planet
Earth that is going to be the most
destructive thing the most destructive
time
ever in the history of the planet we're
not talking about a literal tornado here
we're not talking about literal wins but
these represent Winds of some kind of
strife
put a one in the chat if you're with me
so far
Revelation 7 is not talking about
literal wins being let loose but it's
using the term
symbolically it's used in the term
symbolically now if we go over to
Matthew chapter 24 you will see Jesus
himself describing this time period
Jesus says in Matthew 24 15 talking
about this time when when in my own
words the tornado will hit the tornado
will touch down
he says when you therefore shall see the
abomination of desolation spoken of by
Daniel the Prophet stand in the Holy
Place who swore reader let them
understand then let them which be in
Judea flee into the mountains
let him which is on my house stop not
come down to take anything out of his
house neither let him which is in the
field return back to his to take his
clothes and woe unto them that are with
child and to them that give suck in
those days verse 20 but pray that your
flight be not in the winter neither on
the Sabbath day for then shall be great
tribulations such as what was not since
the beginning of the world to this time
no nor ever shall be and accept those
days should be shortened there should no
flesh be saved but for the elect's sake
those days shall shall be shortened
and I thought about that like when we
were in our house last night and
I was like who knows how long we're
going to be you know at my neighbor's
house I'm gonna bring my computer
my wife was like leave the computer
don't bring the computer
so I'll put the computer on the table
and left it
I want y'all to think about that
Jesus says when this storm hits and
we're not necessarily going to be
talking about well what is the
abomination of desolation don't get
caught up in that right now I just want
you to focus on the time period the time
and what's coming and how how we're told
don't even grab anything you just need
to be ready for that storm you need to
be ready for that world you need to head
for shelter
put a one in the chat if y'all you need
to head for shelter
so so what is this this storm what is
this storm that Jesus is warning that
the Bible is trying to send us text
alerts warnings sirens What is the storm
what does the storm consist of why is it
such a dangerous thing what's in the
storm
that's the question
I want you to notice how Matthew 24 23
continues listen to what the Bible says
then
Jesus continuing to speak says then if
any man shall stand to you low here is
Christ or there believe it not for there
shall arise false Christ and false
prophets and shall show great signs and
wonders in someone said if it were
possible they shall deceive the very
elect now I need y'all to follow this
carefully
the Great
time of trial of danger
consists around being deceived
the storm is a storm of deception put a
one in the chat if you understand what
I'm saying thus far this is not a Christ
is not warning us of a coming storm of
you know I mean yes we know that
according to the Bible they're going to
be natural calamities right earthquakes
and floods Etc but but those were signs
Jesus gave early on
he's talking about in this great time of
trial then be careful because if it were
possible even the very elect
would be what
deceived
deceived let me ask you a question
when someone is deceived by something
I'm gonna see if y'all can this is a
little a little quiz for you and y'all
y'all y'all probably know the answer
already if someone's deceived by
something what is a term that we would
usually use to say you know about them
being involved from the deception
involved in some they shouldn't be
involved in
we typically say hey man don't get
uh don't get what in that don't get
Terry
can you say that again don't get what
just put that in the chat again
everybody look at what Terry just put in
the chat then Terry and I did not confer
beforehand
but just see what Terry said don't get
caught up
now I want you to understand beloved
that when a tornado hits
come on y'all when a tornado hits
and that wind is moving rapidly what's
happening people are getting what caught
up caught up in the wind caught up in
the deception that's what Jesus is
warning it he's saying listen there is
coming a whirlwind that's going to be so
powerful that multitudes are going to
get caught up in it
and not have the power to escape
let me let me let me put it in the way
that Ephesians chapter 4 verse 14 puts
it because Ephesians chapter 4 verse 14
says that we henceforth be no more cat
children
tossed to and fro
and carried about with every come on
y'all
with every what
every wind of Doctrine by the slide of
men and cunning craftiness whereby they
lie and wait to deceive so if we put all
this together what we see here is Jesus
is saying listen the Bible is telling us
look a tornado's coming at the end of
time it hasn't touched down yet because
God is holding back the Four Winds it
hasn't touched down yet but when it hits
it's going to be so powerful it's going
to be so strong that multitudes will be
caught up in these winds these winds
which have to do with not literal wins
but the Winds of Doctrine
deception
false teachings
are y'all with me and beloved I've never
been in a tornado like in an actual
tornado like me myself in the tornado
but I can only imagine that if you're in
the middle of a tornado it must be the
hardest thing to get out of it but let
me tell you something
I wasn't a tornado
there are many people who could raise
their hands right now and say Yes pastor
I was in a tornado but by the grace of
God
by the grace of God
I was pulled from that tornado
of false Doctrine I was pulled from that
tornado of these false winds I was
pulled
are y'all with me
so notice notice what Jesus says in
Matthew chapter 7 verse 21 because the
question is who are the ones that that
are going to get caught up in this
tornado this coming tornado not only the
wicked not only those who are openly
Wicked but notice what the Bible says in
Matthew 27 21.
he says not everyone that's saved unto
me Lord Lord shall enter into the
kingdom of heaven but he that doeth the
will of My Father which is in heaven
many will say to me in that day Lord
Lord have we not prophesied in thy name
and in thy name cast out devils and in
thy name done many wonderful works then
will I profess unto them I never knew
you depart from me you that work what
iniquity
so they're going to be people who are
claiming Christ but when the tornado
hits watch how do you know past how are
you connecting the tornado with this
verse well let me show you because the
very next verse
verse 24
says this
therefore
whosoever heareth these sayings of mine
and do with them
I will liken him unto a wise man which
built his house upon a what
come on put that in the chat for me what
does the wise man build his house upon
put it put the word in the chat for me
the wise man builds his house upon a
a rock
and watch this the rain descended and
the floods came and the what
the winds blew and being upon that house
and it fell not for it was founded upon
a rock
however everyone that that hear these
things of mine and do it than not but
instead of doing my things they are
following false doctrines and the false
teachings everyone that hear these
things of mine and do it then not
so I'll be liking them to a foolish man
which built his house upon the sand
and the Bible says in verse 27 and the
rain descended and the floods came and
the winds blow and beat upon that house
and it fell and great was the fall of it
so
um just give me just put a seven in the
chat y'all if we're all on the same page
right now
all right listen
all I'm telling you right now is that
the Whirlwind that Jesus is warning of
the Whirlwind that the Bible is wanting
of the the tornado that is coming
according to Revelation chapter 7 it has
not touched down on the ground yet and I
learned something really interesting as
I was listening to the um to the
newscaster last night because we had our
our phones on and he was like now listen
I know there's a lot of rain I know
there's heavy wind but the tornado has
not touched down yet and I thought man
that's interesting look at all this rain
look at all this wind like it's bad but
the tornado hasn't even touched down I
was like yeah um
that's deep
because I need y'all to understand
something
as we look at the history of the Bible
and the history of planet Earth and all
the things that have happened Prophecies
of the Bible have talked about things
that are unfolding all those things
beloved are are the rain and the and the
and the floods and the winds but listen
the tornado
has not yet touched down on planet Earth
do you understand what I'm saying
as bad as things may look at certain
times at certain times in history the
tornado has not yet touched so what
we're going to do today is we are going
to because remember all throughout the
day we were getting texts
tornado coming
tornado alert
be prepared I need you to understand
beloved that the word of God
has been texting us
and many people many many people are
ignoring the text
maybe not even understanding the text
but but I need you to understand that
that God so loved the world that is
sending text messages
Bible texts messages
Bible warnings so
what God has done is he is he is see God
God is a
God is the storm chaser
God is the is is is the one that sees
the storm ahead of time and tells us hey
our Storm is Coming
and he Chronicles it in the Bible
he Chronicles it and he's he says look
I'ma show you the history of the storm
so so if you want to know how the storm
gets to where it gets in Revelation
chapter seven we need to go back and ask
well where does a storm begin and
beloved who man I like when the Lord
dropped this on me this morning I was
just like yes yes yes
because the storm beloved begins not
this storm begins it has its origin not
in the Gulf of Mexico
but we're gonna go to another body of
water and I want you to come with me as
we go to the slide Daniel chapter 7 and
verse 1 we are going to learn today
about the origin of this tornado where
does it begin
and the Prophet Daniel tells us in
Daniel chapter 7 verse 1 in the first
year of Del shazar King of Babylon
Daniel had a dream and visions of his
head upon his bed then he wrote the
dream and told us some of the matters
Daniel speaking said I saw in my vision
by night and behold the Four Winds of
the heavens strove upon the great sea
just just come back come back to me for
a moment
I I need y'all to understand something
here
the great sea here is a reference to the
Mediterranean
This Tornado does not start in the Gulf
of Mexico it starts in the body of
waters in the Mediterranean beloved
this
storm has its origin in Daniel 7.
four wins in Revelation chapter seven
four wins in Daniel chapter 7.
and when we look we look at what's going
on in Daniel 7 we see
and then Daniel says in verse 3 and 4
great beasts came up from the sea
diverse one from another so
if I were to ask you where does the
storm start where does this tornado
where do these winds begin to gather
strength your answer is going to be it
begins in Daniel 7. it begins with these
four beasts and I want you to notice
verse three
Daniel 7 verse 3 the Bible says and four
great beasts came up from the sea
diverse one from another the first was
like a lion and had eagles wings I
beheld till the wings were there thereof
were plucked and it was lifted from the
earth and made to stand upon the feet as
a man and a man's heart was given to it
now
if you've never heard this before I just
need you to understand something very
easy to understand here these are not
literal beasts coming up out of the sea
let's look at what the Bible tells us in
Daniel chapter same chapter verse 23.
Dusty said the fourth Beast shall be the
fourth Kingdom upon the Earth so very
simply put a beast in the Bible when
it's used symbolically is used to
represent a kingdom
so these four beasts would represent
four kingdoms are y'all with me
four kingdoms okay so the first Beast
that Daniel sees looks like a lion so
we're looking for a kingdom that the
Bible is referring to here
and and what I want to share with you
we're not going to spend a whole lot of
time hammering down the identity of
these four kingdoms we're gonna try to
do this very quickly because that's not
the focus of today's message
but but to if I can try to simplify this
in this same book
a vision has been given in an earlier
chapter the chapter is Daniel 2. and in
that chapter uh the king of Babylon
Nebuchadnezzar has a dream in which he
sees four kingdoms but instead of it
being represented by beasts it's being
represented by a man a huge image in
fact we go to the screen and we'll see
that Nebuchadnezzar had this dream and
in this dream he saw a huge image of a
man who had the head of gold and then
chest and arms of silver and then
billion thighs of brass and then legs of
iron and clay and so there are four
kingdoms that are being described in
Daniel chapter Two And when Daniel
interprets the stream he tells
Nebuchadnezzar you verse this is verse
38 wheresoever the children of men dwell
the Beast of the field and the files of
the heaven has he given into thine hand
and has made the ruler over them all
thou art this head of gold
so all I want you to see here is
something very simple the Bible
identifies this first Kingdom as the
kingdom of Babylon the kingdom of
Babylon
so if we just follow that that line of
thought this first Beast like a lion
represents Babylon in Daniel 7 verse 5
it says this and behold another Beast a
second light to a bear and it raised
itself upon one side and they had three
ribs in the mouth of it between the
teeth of it and they said doesn't arise
the virus much flesh so
there would be a second Nation rising up
and overthrowing the first nation
Babylon so all we got to do is look at
history and ask what nation is it that
overthrew the Babylonian Empire and the
answer is very simple it was the medo
Persian Empire in fact in Daniel 5 28
we see it's spelled out for us speaking
of the Babylonian Empire it says thy
kingdom is divided and given to the
medes and the Persians so we've got
Babylon followed by the middle Persian
Empire let's keep going Daniel 7 6 after
this I'll be held in low another like a
leopard which had upon the back of it
four wings of a foul the Beast also had
four heads and Dominion was given to it
again we're not going to get into all
the details of why four heads and why
four wings but simple all we need to do
is ask the question
what kingdom overthrew the medo-persian
Empire what kingdom came after medo
Persia and the answer is the Grecian
Empire in fact we find that spelled out
in the Book of Daniel because in the
Book of Daniel chapter 8 another vision
is given showing a ram being defeated by
a he goat notice what the Bible says in
Daniel 8 verse 20. the ram which you saw
having two horns are the kings of media
and Persia watch this and the rough goat
is the king of Grisha and the Great Horn
that is between his eyes is the first
king that would be Alexander the Great
so the Bible is telling us here
prophesying Greece is the kingdom that
will overthrow me to Persia which
according to history is exactly what
happened so the question now is what is
that fourth Kingdom all we need to do in
fact let's go there Daniel 7 verse 7
after this I saw in the night visions
then Behold a fourth Beast Dreadful and
terrible and strong exceeding and it had
great iron teeth and a devoured in
Breaking pieces and stamped the residue
with the feet of it and it was diverse
from all the beasts that were before it
and it had ten horns so I need y'all to
listen carefully
remember in Daniel 2 we said that there
was a parallel Vision the head of gold
the chest and arms of silver media
Persia the belly and thighs of brass
Greece and then the legs of iron roam
the legs of iron parallel this fourth
beast in Daniel 7 the legs of iron are
connected to ten toes the the fourth
Beast of Daniel 7 has ten horns so all
I'm demonstrating here is that Daniel 7
is simply an amplification of Daniel
chapter 2.
that's very important for us to
establish here so so
we know that it was the Roman Empire
that was in existence when Christ came
upon the Earth with that was the Empire
that overthrew the Roman Empire the the
um
The Grecian Empire and that was the
Empire that ultimately destroyed the
Jewish Nation John chapter 11 verse 48
if we let in the salon all men will
believe on him that is Jesus and the
Romans shall come and take away both our
place and our nation so history confirms
that it was the Roman Empire that
overthrew Greece and it was a Roman
Empire that ultimately destroyed
Jerusalem okay are we doing so good so
far
please keep in mind we're talking about
a coming tornado and you might be like
well Pastor I understand that history
but what does it have to do with the
tornado well please follow along here in
Daniel 7 verse 8.
the Bible says I considered the horns
that is the Ten horns that came out of
the Roman Empire and behold there came
up among them another little horn before
whom there were three of the first horns
plucked up by the roots and behold in
this horn were eyes like the eyes of a
man and a mouth-speaking great things so
if I can break this down simply
when Rome fell in around 476 A.D they
were Rome was ultimately divided into
various tribes various Barbarian tribes
which is what is represented by these
ten horns of Daniel 7 or the ten toes of
Daniel 2. and the Bible is telling us
that among out of divided Rome there
would arise this little horn power that
would uproot
three of the kingdoms that came out of
Rome three of these of these kingdoms
that were uh Barbarian tribes
and then it's going to go on to give us
something very specific as to how to
identify this little horn now let me
just tell you right up front that this
little horn is the instigator of the
tornado put a one in the chat if you
understand what I'm saying put a one in
the chat if you understand what you may
not understand who the little horn is
yet but I simply want you to get here
we're talking about the tornado coming
at the End of Time the tornado that's
going to touch down it's a tornado of
deception we learned a tornado of false
doctrine of of Winds of doctrine that
are going to blow every almost everyone
away
blow everyone away
almost everyone away
so what do we do we're still all right
we're going to be storm trackers today
we're going to go back and see where did
the storm begin and lo and behold in the
in the in the great sea we find these
four winds blowing and as a result of
them blowing these nations rise up
rising up in power overthrowing one
another
which ultimately leads
to this little horn power that is going
to do some things
so the first thing I want you to
understand is this
this little horn
the Bible says it would uproot three of
the ten horns if we go to history do we
find that this power actually uprooted
Three Kingdoms out of those that came
out of the Roman Empire and the answer
is absolutely yes those kingdoms on the
screen were the ostragos the vicer gods
the vicer gods and the Harry line
what else the Bible speaks of this same
little horn saying he shall speak great
words against the most high and shall
wear out or persecute the Saints of the
most high and think to change times and
laws now if you're watching
if you're watching I want you to put
those two those that phrase in the chat
change times and laws because that's
what we're going to be focusing on today
Changing Times and laws the Bible says
and they shall be given into his hand
until a time and times and the dividing
of time so let's first focus on this
time time and dividing of time
a Time
in the Bible among other things is
symbolic of a literal year so a time
would be a Jewish year of 360 days times
would be
two years
so that would be 720 years and then the
dividing of time would be half a year or
180 days so times 360 or time
times
720 and the dividing of time 180 you add
it all together and you come up with
1260 days or according to Bible prophecy
a day is symbolic of a year Ezekiel
chapter 4 verse 6 just as a point of
reference there's a whole other study on
this but again I I I'm not focusing in
on the details of this because I want
you to be focused on something else very
important but just see there Ezekiel 4 6
I've appointed V each day for a year so
this 1260 days would actually be 1260
years
we're looking for a power
that would be a religious power
rising out of Rome that would dominate
Europe for over a thousand years and
beloved listen to me carefully
there is only one
entity that fits that description
rising up just around the far or coming
into power Just Around the fall of the
Roman Empire
dominating all of Europe
persecuting those who profess to be
followers of God while claiming to be a
follower of God themselves
it is the papal power
the papacy
the system
why is God why is the Bible pointing out
this system well first of all
we need to focus on times
so what
does the bible mean by this little horn
would think to change times well come
with me to First Thessalonians chapter 5
verse 1. notice what the Bible says here
but of the times but of the times and
the seasons
but of the times and the seasons but of
the times and the seasons Brethren you
have no need that I write unto you for
yourselves know perfectly that the day
of the Lord so cometh as a thief in the
night for when they shall say peace and
safety then sudden destruction coming
upon that comes cometh upon them as
travail upon a woman with child and they
shall not Escape so what I want you to
see clearly here is that the times and
Seasons being spoken of here
symbolize prophetic time put that in the
chat for me please
the times and Seasons referred here
refer to prophetic times
Jesus said in Matthew chapter 16 verse 2
he answered and said unto them when it
is evening you say it will be fair
weather for the sky is red and in the
morning it will be foul weather today
for the sky is red and lowering all ye
Hypocrites you can discern the face of
the sky but cannot you discern the signs
of the the signs of the what
the signs of the times
so just to recap and just to make sure
we're on the same page we need to
understand that that that when we're
talking about times in the Bible we're
talking about prophetic times we're
talking about prophetic periods we're
talking about things that God has
prophesied
would come to pass
notice with me Acts chapter 17 verse 26
the Bible says that God has made of one
blood all nations of men for to dwell on
all the face of the Earth and has
determined the times before appointed
so who is it that determines the times
before appointed who is it that does
that that determines the times it is God
that does that
it is God that sets forth prophetic
times it is God that foretells what's
coming to pass and this is what we would
call Doctrine true Doctrine true
teaching the prophetic word of God it's
God's text messages to humanity hey look
out for this look out for this because
this is coming and this is how the devil
is going to try to deceive you
he's going to try to get you caught up
in the Whirlwind but I am sending you
text messages
to show you so that you will not be
caught off guard so that you will not be
caught up
in the tornado
here's something interesting if we go
back to Daniel chapter 2 when
Nebuchadnezzar has his dream and none of
the wise men can understand the dream or
interpret it or give the future events
then Daniel goes to pray and he gets the
understanding of the dream and notice
what Daniel says here Lotus Daniel 2
verse 18.
So Daniel
uh went it says that they would desire
the mercies of God of Heaven concerning
the secret
that Daniel and his fellow should not
perish with the rest of the wise men of
Babylon then was the secret revealed
unto Daniel in a night vision watch this
then Daniel blessed the god of Heaven
Daniel answered and said blessed be the
name of God forever and ever for wisdom
and might are his verse 21
and
he
changes
the what everybody
God changes the times and the seasons he
removed Kings and setteth up Kings he
giveth wisdom unto the wise and
knowledge to them that no understanding
he revealed the Deep secret the deep and
secret things and he knoweth what is in
darkness and the light dwelleth with him
so what I want you to see here
is that God is the one who is able to to
to to to control the times and the
seasons why because he's God
so when the Bible says that the little
horn will think to change times meaning
times and Seasons it's pointing to
something very specific you all it's
pointing to changing prophecy
so that people get caught up in false
prophecy
put a five in the chat
put a five in the chat if you are
following what I'm saying
in other words
this system would begin to teach and
manipulate the word of God
to where it is now teaching things that
the Bible does not say is going to
happen
it is manipulating prophecy and changing
very good rig it is changing
the prophetic understanding of God's
people now let me just build on this
very quickly then we're gonna keep
moving because what's interesting about
this is that it is this system that
introduced
two schools of Prophecy called preterism
meaning
don't worry about the Book of Revelation
because the entire Book of Revelation
was fulfilled in the past there's
nothing left to be fulfilled it was all
fulfilled
by 100 A.D
so there's nothing really important in
us for the in the Book of Revelation for
us now that's called the school of
preterism while the other school
futurism teaches that hey all the
Prophecies of Daniel of Daniel in
Revelation are in the future after the
church has raptured away so they're not
pointing to now in fact they're not even
relevant to God's people because we'll
be gone by the time all these things
come to pass
and what's interesting about this is
that the reason why
this system
thought to change prophetic times is
because the reformers began to look at
this very system and say wait a minute
you are the Fulfillment
of Bible prophecy you are the very
system that Daniel 7 25 was talking
about
and in order to try to get that
prophetic finger off of the church they
they devised two new schools of Prophecy
one saying don't worry about prophecy
now because it was all fulfilled in the
past preterism or hey it will all be
fulfilled in the future
so when you hear things about the seven
year treaty and things of this nature
these are all teachings
whirlwinds tornadoes
that have millions of people caught up
in them
and this is before the tornado has even
touched down beloved
come on follow me second Peter 1 19.
this is what the Bible says
we have also a more sure word of
Prophecy where unto you do well that you
take heed as until a light that shineth
in a dark place until the day Dawn and
the day star arise in your heart God is
trying to tell us that prophecy is what
is going to help us
not be carried away by the Whirlwind
now
here's what
raise your hand if you're saying I don't
want to be caught up in that Whirlwind
of deception
while God says prophecy
if you don't want to get caught up in
that Whirlwind of deception you better
understand the texts that I'm sending
you
particularly from the books of Daniel
and revelation
I need you to understand these texts
because I'm warning you of the coming
storm are y'all with me
are you following
so now watch this the Bible says in
Revelation 19 10 and I felt his feet to
worship him and he said unto me see that
I'll do it not I'm thy fellow servant
and of thy Brethren that have the
testimony of Jesus worship God for the
testimony of Jesus is the spirit of
Prophecy so so now we're going to focus
in Beloved
on this idea of the spirit of Prophecy
the spirit of Prophecy which is the
testimony of Jesus the devil doesn't
want you understanding the spirit of
Prophecy the spirit he put in the
prophets Daniel
John
Ezekiel
Isaiah Jeremiah he doesn't want the
world
understanding this prophecy this Spirit
of Prophecy
so the Bible tells in revelation 22 18
watch this
for I testify unto every man that Hearth
the words of the prophecy of this book
If any man shall add unto these things
God shall add unto him the plagues that
are written in this book and if any man
shall take away from the words of the
book of this prophecy God shall take
away his part out of The Book of Life in
other words beloved God does not want
anybody Changing Times
prophetic times
but the Bible says that this little horn
would do just that okay so now we've got
times down we know okay this little horn
power is going part of the Heart part of
the tornado
is is the tornado of false prophecy
put a seven in the chat
put a seven in the chat if you
understand what I'm saying part of the
world win of deception at the end of
time will be based upon false prophecy
the changing of times prophetic times
now what about the law
Changing Times and laws
well in John chapter 14 15 Jesus says
this if you love me
keep my Commandments
if you love me
keep my Commandments that's what he says
John 14 15 John 15 10. if you keep my
Commandments you shall abide in my love
even as I have kept my father's
Commandments and abide in his love
yeah very simple first John 2 3 and
hereby we do know that we know him if we
keep his Commandments he that save I
know him and keepeth not he's a command
not his Commandments is a liar and the
truth is not in him so let's come back
to the screen and I want you to notice
something now remember
what did we just see
the testimony of Jesus is the spirit of
what
prophecy that's what we just read
two verses ago the testimony of Jesus is
the spirit of Prophecy the devil is
angry with the spirit of Prophecy he
doesn't want people understanding the
testimony of Jesus which is a spirit of
Prophecy but he also hates people who
keep the Commandments of God
how do we know that very simple y'all
Revelation 12 17 notice what the Bible
says and the dragon was rough
or angry with the woman meaning the
church and went to make war with the
remnant of her seed now notice the two
things which keep the Commandments of
God
the law
and the testimony of Jesus Christ
prophecy
prophetic times okay
come back with me I need you to
we need to hammer this down y'all
Daniel 7 the little horn is going to
manipulate times prophetic times and
laws what laws God's laws
that's what we read in Daniel 7 25 we go
over to the very last book of the Bible
Revelation and we see we see the dragon
is angry
with those
who have the testimony of Jesus
or or
they they embrace the testimony of Jesus
which means the spirit of Prophecy the
prophetic word of God and who keep the
Commandments of God
are y'all catching this
so now we know
that anyone who is against the law of
God and anyone who has bought into false
prophecies are are those who are caught
up in the Whirlwind
and I need you to understand beloved
that God is trying to save as many
people as he can from this whirlwind
watch this Matthew 5 17 think not that
I'm come to destroy the law or the
prophets pause y'all pause
did you catch this did you catch us
think not that I'm come to destroy the
law or the prophets
what is little horn trying to do destroy
the law and the prophecy
Changing Times the prophets and laws the
law Jesus says look don't think that
I've come to destroy the law and the
prophets no that's the little horn
the little horn is going to attempt to
change times prophetic times prophecy
and laws but
um
but
I have sent you text messages already
telling you this now I know it's crazy
to me
what's crazy to me is how God can
actually send a text message from the
past
and people look at that text message and
say no the Law's done away with no we
don't have to keep the law no you know
it's mind-blowing why would God warn of
this entity thinking to change times
prophecy and laws and then we turn
around and be like oh the law has been
done away with yeah beloved we need to
be more mindful of how we treat the
Bible how we treat the New Testament
things that we think oh the Bible's
saying this when when in actuality it's
not saying that thing at all
so so now the question becomes watch
this verse 18 for verily I say unto you
till Heaven and Earth pass not one job
in any wise pass from the law to all be
fulfilled whosoever shall break one of
these least Commandments and shall teach
them and so shall be called lease in the
Kingdom of Heaven but whosoever shall do
and teach them the same Shall be Called
great in the Kingdom of Heaven so my
question is
do we have evidence of the little horn
changing laws let's go to the screen and
I'm not going to take too long on this
we're just going to read we're just
going to read
question this is from a doctrinal
catechism Third Edition page 174
authored by Stephen Keenan question have
you any other way of proving that the
church has power to Institute festivals
or precepts answer Hatchet not such
power
she could not have done that in which
all modern religion disagree with her
she could not have substituted the
observance of Sunday the first day of
the week for the observance of Saturday
the seventh day of the week a change for
which there is no scriptural Authority
let's keep moving
the conference catechism of Catholic
Doctrine 1957 published page 50. for
example nowhere in the Bible do we find
that Christ or the apostles ordered that
the Sabbath be changed from Saturday to
Sunday we have a commandment of God by
giving to Moses to keep holding the
Sabbath day that is the seventh day of
the week Saturday today most Christians
keep Sunday because it has been revealed
to us by the Roman Catholic church
outside the Bible
I need y'all to catch this
is a whirlwind y'all I want you to think
about how many people are caught in this
Whirlwind well-meaning people good
people
but they're caught up in this whirlwind
a whirlwind that the Bible predicted
how about this I have repeatedly offered
one thousand dollars to anyone who can
prove to me from the Bible alone that
I'm bound to keep Sunday holy
there is no such law in the Bible it is
the law of the Holy Catholic Church
alone the Bible says remember the
Sabbath day to keep it holy the Catholic
Church says and by the way this is a
Catholic Source the Catholic Church says
no by my divine power I abomish the
Sabbath day and command you to keep holy
the first day of the week and lo the
entire civilized World bows down in a
reverent obedience to the command of the
Holy Catholic Church
keep moving let's keep moving
Protestants do not realize that by
observing Sunday they accept the
authority of the spokesperson of the
church the Pope
one more
two more actually of course the Catholic
Church claims that the change Saturday
Sabbath to Sunday was her act and the
ACT is a mark of her ecclesiastical
Authority in religious things one more
the pope has power to change times and
abrogate laws when I first read this I
was like nah come on are you serious
the pope has power to change it's like
literally quoting Daniel 7 25 y'all
the pope has power to change times to
abrogate laws and to dispense with all
things even the precepts of Christ the
pope has Authority as and has often
exercises to dispense with the
Commandment of Christ you guys
I'm not even gonna there's no or there
should be no argument there's not an
argument as to this commandment there's
no argument the question is are you
caught up in the Whirlwind are you
caught up in the tornado that's the
question
and beloved if you are guess what God
loves you and he desires to pull you
from that Whirlwind he desires to pull
you from that tornado now I need you to
follow this because what we're seeing is
that there's little horn power through
which the Whirlwind began to stir began
to gain strength began over the sea
it began over the sea and it dominated
for over a thousand years bringing us
roughly down to the late 1700s now this
is why when you go to Revelation Chapter
13 Verse 1 you see John like recapping
what Daniel talked about John says I
stood upon the sand of the sea and saw a
beast rise above the sea having seven
heads and ten horns and upon his horns
ten crowns and upon his heads the name
of blasphemy this is the same power in
verse 5 there was given unto him a mouth
speaking great and blasph great things
in blasphemies and power was given unto
him to continue 40 and two months that's
the same time period as the 1260 years
now
why am I bringing that up because y'all
and here's where we're about to like get
really deep all right everything up to
this point was just a setup
I need y'all to understand this
in Revelation chapter 13 verse 11 listen
to me
that which began over the sea
hit dry land
um
that which began
over the Great Sea in Daniel 7 by the
time we get to Revelation 13 11 it has
now hit dry land now hitting dry land
doesn't mean that the tornado has
touched down it simply means that the
winds are now prophetically speaking
over dry land Pastor what are you
talking about watch this Revelation 13
verse 11 and I beheld another Beast
coming up out of the earth and he had
two horns like a lamb
and he spake as a dragon watch this he
exercises all the power of the first
Beast before him so the question is
first of all who is this other Beast
Revelation 13 11 says that this Beast is
rising up at the time that the first
Beast received its deadly wound so we're
looking for a nation that would come
upon the scene in the late 1700s that
would profess to be a lamb-like Nation
meaning we follow Jesus because the lamb
is a symbol of Christ in the Bible
however it would speak like a dragon and
in fact exercise the power of the first
Beast before it which points to the
papacy where talking beloved about the
nation of America but more specifically
protestantism within America
and now we see that that that the
Protestant churches of America that that
at one time protested against the the
errors of the of the papal system the
the false the the the the Winds of the
papal system have now by and large
embraced
those wings
are y'all following me the the storm
now hits dry land it's just symbolic
language
what it's what the Bible's telling us is
that protestantism who at one time when
when in the days of Martin Luther and
and and Wesley and and Wycliffe where
they understood wait a minute
something's going on these doctrines
aren't biblical we're looking at the
Bible and we believe in the Bible and
the Bible only at some point they lost
their protest and embraced these very
doctrines
brought upon the World by the first
Beast
so the Bible is now revealing to us that
this second beast is doing the very same
thing that the first piece did and by
the way beloved if you want to know why
so many Skeptics of the Bible so many
atheists have turned from God it's
because of what they see in the first
Beast that kid the wins that came out of
the sea that eventually hit the Earth
they're looking
they're looking at the confusion
and they're saying they believe they
think oh this is really what the Bible
teaches and so that I don't want
anything to do with the Bible
so so watch this note how Revelation 14
puts this Revelation 14 verse 8. watch
this the Bible says they're following
another Angel saying Babylon has fallen
has fallen that great City because she
made all nations
drink of the wine of the wrath of her
fornication
okay
so what does that mean drink of the wine
so let me ask a question
when you drink wine no no no no I'm not
going to ask it let's just read what the
Bible says what do you think it means
what do you think it means to drink what
to be drunk
how does Babylon make all nations drink
of the wine or how does Babylon catch
the whole world up in this Whirlwind in
this tornado
This Tornado of Lies This Tornado of
Deceit
remember the tornado has not touched
down yet the winds are the storm is here
the the the the the winds are blowing
but the tornado it's not full force the
tornado has not yet touched down that is
still yet future
but check this out Isaiah 29 Isaiah 29
verse 9.
the Bible says stay yourselves and
wonder cry ye out and cry they are
drunken but not with wine they stagger
but not with strong drink for the Lord
has poured out upon you the spirit of
deep sleep and has closed your eyes the
prophets and your rulers and the seers
has he covered and the vision of all is
becoming to you as a as words of a book
that is sealed which men deliver to one
that is learned saying read this I pray
thee and he says I cannot for it is
sealed and the book is delivered to him
that is not learned saying read as I
pray thee and he says I am not I cannot
I am not learned verse 13 wherefore the
Lord said for as much as his people draw
near me with their mouth and with their
lips do honor me but they have removed
their heart far from me and their fear
toward me is taught by the precepts of
men listen to what God is saying
the drunkenness
simply means you can't understand
have you ever tried to study when you're
Dr when you're drunk don't don't put a
one in the chat don't don't put anything
okay but I'm just asking
what do you think it'd be like to try to
study material when you're drunk you're
not going to have understanding what God
is saying
is that those who are drunk with the
wine of Babylon
are two are in a drunken state that they
cannot comprehend the truth they cannot
comprehend the prophecy they cannot
comprehend that the law of God is not
done away with cannot be changed
you're you're thinking in a drunken way
there is no clarity
Jesus almost quotes this very verse look
at what he says in Matthew 5 7 ye
Hypocrites well did Isaiah prophesy of
you saying this people draws nigh unto
me with their mouth and honoreth me with
their lips but their heart is far from
me watch this for in vain they do
worship me teaching for doctrines the
Commandments of men
teaching for doctrines the Commandments
of men beloved we must understand God is
trying to get us to understand by
sending us the text message saying hey
guys listen I'm sending you a warning
there's going to be a power that rises
that's going to claim to have authority
to change my law
when you see this power do that very
thing remember the text that I sent you
what text Lord remember Daniel 7 25
remember the text I sent you
he sent the text to all of us but so
many of us are ignoring the text and
therefore we don't understand the
prophecy
that God has sent to wake people up and
get them to shelter before the tornado
hits so now the question becomes this
how do the righteous not get caught up
in the storm that's the question how do
the righteous not get caught up in the
storm well the answer is we already read
the answer notice again with me Matthew
7 24 therefore whosoever hear these
sayings of mine and do with them I will
liken him onto a wise man which built
his house upon a rock
and the rain descended and the floods
came and the winds blew and beat up on
that house and it fell not for it was
founded upon a rock beloved come back
with me listen to me how do we avoid
being blown away when the tornado
touches down
it's by building our house
on the rock
I see an answer in the chat that I don't
even want to say anything because the
person black the person has already beat
me to the answer but I just I I got I
gotta build this up
I gotta build this up
y'all about to see something powerful
here listen to me
The Rock
yes Clint is our refuge
our refuge from what our refuge from the
storm our refuge from the winds our
refuge from the coming tornado
listen to what the Bible says here
in Isaiah 26 verse 4. trustee in the
Lord forever for in the Lord Jehovah is
Everlasting strength now check this out
y'all that word for strength there is
the Hebrew right there properly a cliff
a sharp Rock generally a rock or Boulder
strength
let me read that same verse of another
translation
the ASV trustee in Jehovah forever for
in Jehovah even Jehovah is an
everlasting Rock
or how about this one the Bible in basic
English let your hope be in the Lord
forever for the Lord jaw is an
unchanging Rock now I'm a
on
changing Rock here's what I want you to
understand
the reason why one of the reasons why
God
uses the rock as an analogy of himself
is because he wants to help us
understand that though that he is
unchanging put that word in the chat for
me please he is what everyone
he is unchanging
he is he is The Rock he is
unchanging put that word in the chat he
is unchanging come with me to second
Samuel 22 verse 2. the Bible says he
said the Lord is my rock and my Fortress
and my deliverer the god of my rock and
him will I trust he is my shield and the
Horn of my salvation he is my high tower
and my refuge my storm shelter y'all
my storm shelter
My Savior thou saveth me from violence
what the violent vortex
that's why we need to run to the Rock
again second Samuel 22 verse 32 we're
almost there we're all we're about to
wrap up
we're making our initial descent
make sure your seat belts are wrong
second Samuel 22 verse 32 for who is God
save the Lord and who is a rock Save Our
God verse 47 the Lord liveth and blessed
be my rock and exalted be the god of the
rock of my salvation God beloved is a
rock God is a rock second Samuel 23
verse three the god of Israel said the
rock of Israel speak to me he that
ruleth over man must be just ruling in
the fear of God God is the rock of
Israel now
now
I want y'all to note this with me
Deuteronomy 32 verse 4 the Bible says he
is the rock his work is perfect
for all his ways are judgment a god of
Truth and without iniquity just and
right to see so God is our Rock and his
work is what
perfect
so let me ask you a question let's come
back to the screen here I'm asking a
question
when the Bible says God's work is
perfect what does that mean
when God does something
is good
God's work
is perfect
so if I were to say that about me my
work is perfect right
um y'all would be like okay uh what can
you show me some of your work and I
might say hey I'm gonna take you into my
uh studio
and you you would you know look at the
studio and say hey pretty good but it's
not perfect it's not flawless
right
now if I said my work is perfect but
someone else came and did the studio and
I said my work is perfect with my studio
count as my work being perfect
no that's not my work somebody else did
that
so so let me ask you something
let's just go to Exodus 32 Exodus 32
verse 15. let's notice what the Bible
says here and Moses turned and went down
from the mount and the two tables of the
testimony were in his hand the tables
were written on both their sides on the
one side and on the other were they
written and the tables were the work of
God
and the writing
was the writing of God
Graven upon the tables not let me ask
you a question
let me ask you a question
um
if God if the work of God is his Ten
Commandments
would you call that work complete
perfect
put a one in the chat if you'd call That
Word Perfect
now listen God didn't God didn't create
this television man did that
right yeah man did that with the with
this with with their brains which God
gave them their brains but the
television is not the work of God
are y'all with me
um this microphone is not the work of
God this is the work of men
the work of God
that which God hewed out
himself
which God wrote up himself that is
perfect and what we just read earlier is
that God Matt God connects himself as
God manifests himself or use the symbol
of a rock to show hey I'm unchanging
why does he write The Law of God on a
rock come on y'all
rock because what he's saying is this is
an extension of who I am
the law of God is the very description
of my character the law is perfect
converting the soul so when the enemy
when this system comes in and says the
law can be changed what it's saying is
God is not perfect
God can be improved upon
the law of God beloved cannot be changed
but he tells us the little horn will
think to do that and many are going to
get caught up thinking it's not a big
deal oh it doesn't matter and it'll be
all kinds of drunken reasoning
but God said listen I sent you a text
you didn't get my text don't you hate
that somebody send you a text or you
send somebody a text that oh man I
didn't see your text
in the Judgment God's gonna be like you
didn't get my text
you didn't see my you didn't see all
those texts I sent you in Daniel and
Revelation and Matthew you didn't see
any of those texts
man I did but uh
I didn't you know I didn't think those
texts were for me
notice what job says here job 19 verse
23 oh that my words were now written oh
that they were printed in a book
that they were Graven with an iron pen
and led in the rock forever why is Job
saying oh that my words were great with
an iron pen and led in the rock forever
because job understands the concept that
when something is written in stone when
something is written in the rock that
means it is forever
it is forever
so what I need you to understand is that
this final Whirlwind that's going to
touch down will will will revolve around
this idea that the law of God has been
changed or that the law of God does not
need to be kept and also a false
understanding of Prophecy
listen
there is coming a Time
where the tornado is going to touch down
I want you to come with me Daniel 11
verse 40. we're almost there y'all
Daniel 11 verse 40. the Bible says and
at the time of the end shall the King of
the South push at him and the King of
the North shall come against him like a
whirlwind with chariots and with
Horsemen and with many ships and he
shall enter into the countries and shall
overflow and pass over now I know many
of you have read like what is this
talking about oh I'm just gonna I'm just
gonna say this very simple
Daniel 11 40
leads to Daniel 12 verse 1. in Daniel 12
1 you have Michael standing up you have
the dead being raised and you have a
time of trouble
so all I want you to understand is that
whoever this King of the North is that
comes like a whirlwind with chariots and
Horsemen it's the same power that is
described in verse 44 as doing this
Tidings out of the East and out of the
North shall trouble him therefore he
shall go forth with great Fury
to destroy and utterly to make a way
with many
this is when the tornado touches down
y'all many of you watching right now you
may have no Daniel 11 this King of the
North where'd that come from All I'm
gonna say
is that at the very end of time
this entity known as the King of the
North touches down this is when the
tornado touches down and this is the
Whirlwind that's going to take the World
by storm and please listen carefully to
me
the Whirlwind will be directed at those
who refuse
to drink of the false prophecies
and who refuse to buy the false teaching
that the law of God has been done away
with
how do they how do the righteous
withstand this this tornado
by standing on the rock
by building their house on the rock
meaning they've built their house on
Jesus
the testimony of Jesus which is the
spirit of Prophecy and they have built
their house
on the Commandments of God
those who keep the law of God
those who have the spirit of Prophecy
do not have to fear the Whirlwind
because what whatever the devil brings
we're gonna say
one thing I know is that the law of God
cannot be changed and one thing I know
is that the word of the prophets and
what the prophets taught through Daniel
and revelation will come to pass
see
in Revelation 12 17 remember who the
dragon is angry with those who keep the
Commandments of God and have the
testimony of Jesus and here's what I
want you to see I gotta think we got
like three or four slides left follow me
carefully okay when Jesus comes y'all
and Matthew 24 31 in Matthew 24 31 the
Bible says he shall send his angels with
a great sound of a trumpet they shall
gather together his elect from the Four
Winds
God is gonna rescue us from the tornado
God is going to rescue his people out of
those winds God is going to say no y'all
the winds y'all couldn't take them away
spiritually they stood for me they stood
for the law they stood for what they
understood to be true they stood for the
truth and I'm coming
I'm coming to get my people and I'm
gathering them from the Four Winds now
remember I told you how Daniel 7
was a parallel to Daniel 2. remember I
told you that
if you go back to Daniel 2
remember how we saw that there was a
stone in fact let me go there Daniel 2
verse 34.
the image in Daniel 2 the image of the
man with the head of gold chest storms
of silver begging thighs of brass legs
of iron that image was destroyed by a
stone
cut out without hands cut out of the
side of a mountain the Bible says in
Daniel 2 verse 34 thou saws till about a
stone was cut out without hands which
smold the image upon the feet that were
of iron and clay and break them to
Pieces interesting a stone cut out of a
mountain in fact in verse 45 it says for
as much as you saw that the stones cut
out of the mountain without hands I'm
asking all the question
can you think of anywhere else else in
the Bible where a stone was cut out of a
mountain without human hands
come on y'all help me just put it in the
chat
where else in the Bible do we find a
stone being cut out without human hands
out of a mountain
yes yo it is the law of God the Ten
Commandments Exodus 32 16 and the tables
were the work of God and the writing of
God was Graven upon the tables what we
have beloved is a picture an image of
the Ten Commandments this is what the
world will be judged by their rejection
of the law of God this is why
Ecclesiastes 12 13 says let us hear the
conclusion of the whole matter fear God
and keep his Commandments for this is
the whole duty of man for God shall
bring every work into judgment with
every secret thing whether it be good or
whether it be evil this is why I beloved
at the very end of time
there is a special message going forth
there is an angel in Revelation chapter
14 6 the Bible says I saw another angel
fly in the midst of Heaven having the
Everlasting gospel to preach unto them
that Dawn on the earth and to Every
Nation Kindred tongue and people saying
with a loud voice fear God and give
glory to him for the hour of his
judgment has come and worship him that
made Heaven the Earth the sea and The
Fountains of water beloved this
prophetic message this prophetic angel
this prophetic message is going in the
midst of the storm and calling people to
say listen
keep the Commandments of God for this is
the whole duty of man the Everlasting
gospel beloved at the end of time is
designed to pull people out of the
tornado of false deceptions
and the question
that I have for you today
I note this note the verse
if you just go back and see what that
Angel's message was worship him that
made Heavenly Earth the sea and all that
in them is he's quoting directly from
Exodus 20 verse 11 which is about the
Sabbath commandment where it says for in
six days the Lord made Heaven and Earth
the sea and all that in them is and rest
at the seventh day wherefore God bless
the seventh day and hallowed it
the end time message beloved is pointing
people to keep the Commandments of God
and have the testimony of Jesus here's
my closing verse
Proverbs 18 10 the name of the Lord is a
strong tower
the righteous runeth into it
and is safe
as we were running last night we didn't
have a long way to run
we didn't have a long way to run but we
were running last night
and
as I've thought about it this morning
wow
God says I will be your shelter in the
time of storm
I will be your strong tower I will be
your rock I will be your hiding place I
will be that cleft in the rock
and here's what I believe is happening
we are the testimony earlier today
of two people
who were caught up in the Whirlwind
caught up in the tornado
four years caught up in the tornado
and the spirit of God
rescued them
from that whirlwind
God is pulling people out of confusion
out of Babylon out of error out of false
teachings out of false doctrines he is
pulling people from all around the globe
he's pulling them out of error he's
pulling them out of spiritual Babylon
into the truth
and I'm going to plead with you today if
you're hearing this message for the
first time I'm going to put a link up in
the chat if you're a saint Pastor I need
to study this out I want to study it out
I want to give my life to the Lord in
you I want to start keeping the Sabbath
I want to be baptized I didn't
understand this truth and and now I want
to give my life fully this is what I've
been looking for
if that's you we're going to put a link
up in the chat right now link is going
to go in the chat for you to reach out
to Rick that's our Bible worker and I
think it just went up on the screen
but I would listen
God
is is he is on the move
God is on the move
and the question is will you move with
him
will you follow the leading of his
spirit
will you follow the rock will you build
your house upon the rock or will you
build upon the sand
we're going to put that link in the chat
there it is
you want you want to get deeper into the
Bible
you want to understand this truth you
just heard today we have a whole
playlist by the way we have a whole
playlist of of Truth
it's called the share the truth playlist
I'm going to invite you if you have not
if this is your first time watching go
to that playlist and just watch
everything that has been done so far
over the last several months it it will
change it will bring you an
understanding of the word of God that
will revolutionize your life you
understand me
all right so there it is in the chat I'm
gonna plead with you
I don't want you to just make a decision
and say yes I'd like to I want you to
follow up I want you to get in touch
with our Bible worker and I want you to
to let our Bible worker know hey I want
to be baptized I want to study I want to
understand this truth in a deeper way
and beloved we're going to follow up on
that because you know what our mission
is about saving people from tornadoes
that's why we storm Chase
that's why because we want people to be
Walking In Truth walking in light
walking in righteousness and not being
led astray by false systems and by the
way I'm talking about false systems I'm
not talking about people this is nothing
against individuals who have been a part
of any of these systems it's the system
y'all and not the people are you
understanding what I'm saying God is
calling his people he he's got genuine
people in all of these systems but he's
calling his people out of these systems
come out of her my people that's his
call Heavenly Father
thank you Lord
for speaking to us today thank you Lord
for the power of your word thank you
Lord for for tracking this coming
tornado and showing us what we need to
do to find shelter when this storm hits
Lord may we be prepared may we build our
houses upon the rock that when the winds
come when the rains fall when the floods
come Lord our houses will stand
because they are founded upon the rock
of the law and the prophets the
testimony of Jesus Christ and the
Commandments of God please Lord write
these things in our hearts and may we be
ready
and protected when that tornado touches
down we pray this in Jesus name amen and
amen
we do want to invite you to join us for
the after uh for the Afterglow there's
the altar live link please join us on
the altar live link we're going to talk
about the testimony from this morning
we're going to talk about the sermon you
guys will be able to share your thoughts
and let's build and help one another and
um by the grace of God let's continue
our move on
um
God bless you and uh have a good rest of
your day
thank you for worshiping with us today
if this is your first time visiting with
us we invite you to check out our
website at livingmanna.live there you
will learn more about our mission to
reach the world with the Gospel of Jesus
we have exciting live programs
throughout the week covering topics like
physical health mental health prayer
learning how to prove God's existence
and much more if you would like to
support the ministry you can click on
the tithe and offering link on our
website we ask that you continue to pray
for the church as God continues to open
doors for our programming to reach the
world thank you again for your prayers
and your support
thank you